globalhardwares.com 2003-12-06

# Hardwarexpo Network

| 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

|  | 

**Our Commitment To Your Privacy**

Hardwarexpo.com are committed to respecting your privacy, and providing a secure environment in which you can participate in on-line activities is important to us. This Policy discloses our privacy practices and expresses our commitment to keeping you informed of the information we collect and how it is used. We ask that you take time to read it carefully. We may update this Policy from time to time to reflect new uses, rules, regulations or technologies that impact your privacy. We recommend that users review our Policy on a routine basis to view any changes.  
  
---|---  
|  **The Information We Collect And How It Is Used**

You make the decision whether or not to proceed with any activity that requests personal information, but please be aware that if you choose not to provide the information requested, you may not be able to complete certain transactions with Hardwarexpo. 

Sometimes, such as when you register for a service, order a product, or make other inquiries, we may ask for specific information about you in order to provide that product or service to you. We may need certain personally identifiable information such as name, contact information, and transaction and credit card information. Also, to tailor subsequent communications to you and to continually improve Hardwarexpo offerings, we may also ask you to provide information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, past experience with Hardwarexpo products and services, and detailed contact preferences.

We may periodically conduct both business and individual user surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve our products and services. Participation in such surveys is completely voluntary, and any personal information submitted in response to a survey will remain strictly confidential. 

Data you submit online may also be combined with other information you provide through other means of communication, such as postal mail.

Some Hardwarexpo Web pages use cookies. Cookies are small data files that are transferred from a Web server to your browser. This file contains information that may later be read back by the Web server for record keeping purposes. Use of cookies is standard on the Web and can improve the service a Web site provides to you because content can be prepared to suit your preferences. Cookies are useful, for example, to facilitate a regular visitor's use of a site by eliminating the need to repeatedly type in a password, and to store preferences on a personalized site. This type of information is not used to personally identify an individual, and you remain anonymous. You may modify your browser to reject cookies or to notify you whenever a cookie is sent to your hard drive. If you reject a cookie sent by SmartForce, you may still access the site, but such access may be limited.  
  
|  **Sharing Of Information**

Hardwarexpo will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to others. Unless Hardwarexpo has your permission or is required by law, Hardwarexpo will only share the personal data you provide online with other Hardwarexpo entities and/or outside contractors who may be used to ship products, provide technical support, handle order processing, or otherwise act on Hardwarexpo's behalf for the purpose of providing products and services.

Please remember that when you submit information to a discussion group or some other public forum, the information submitted will be deemed public information and will not be considered confidential.   
  
|  **Data Security**

Hardwarexpo is committed to ensuring the security of your information. We use encryption technology, privacy protection controls and restrictions on employee access in order to safeguard your personal information. 

Every Hardwarexpo employee must abide by our Privacy Policy. Only authorized personnel will have access to your personal information and such access is limited to a need-to-know basis. If, for example, you call us with a concern or complaint, the Hardwarexpo representative is allowed to access the personal information that s/he requires to address your particular concern.  

|  **Links**

Hardwarexpo may provide you with links to other sites. Please be aware that Hardwarexpo is not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. Hardwarexpo does not endorse them or make any representations about them or any information, services, products or materials found on them. If you decide to access any of the third party sites through links, we strongly encourage you to read their privacy statements.  

|  **How To Access And Correct Your Information**

Hardwarexpo strives to keep your personally identifiable information accurate and up-to-date. Should you find inaccuracies in your personally identifiable information, please contact us through one of the communication methods described below.  

|  **Notification Of Changes**

Hardwarexpo reserves the right to make changes to this policy. In the event there is a major change in our privacy practices, a notice will be posted on our web site.   

|  **Contacting Us With Comments And Concerns**

We welcome your comments. Should you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us: via email at [support@Hardwarexpo.com](mailto:support@Hardwarexpo.com), by telephone at (0086)579-2397911,or by mail to: ChinaPackNetwork, Attn: Hardwarexpo Privacy Coordinator, No.69 Bayi Sourth Street, Jinhua City, Zhejiang Province 321010 P.R.C
